欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内 字幕广告招租 商业合作Q:1585235535
不可以 不接受
PROTESTERS: Not all right, not okay!
没有助教就不能处 不可以
We don't have no teachers' aides! Not all right...
不想打岔 但是我们口号
Not to be that guy, but should we really
不符合语法合适吗
be doing non- grammatical chants?
感谢的你的建议 斯科特
Thank you for your input, Scott
那这样呢
How about this?
不可以 不接受
Not all right, not okay.
我们面临严重的助教缺乏
We have a complete lack of teachers' aides.
谢谢
Thank you.
我得进去一趟
I'm going inside.
尿急
I got to pee.
不行 别别别
Ah- ah- ah, no, no, no, no!
你不能去罢工警戒线对面尿尿
You can't pee across the picket line.
如果你非得要去 就去街那头的加油站
If you got to go, go to the gas station up the street.
但你得消费才行 所以帮我带杯咖啡
But you got to buy something, so get me some coffee.
那家可是在湖畔大道上
That- that is all the way down on Lake Avenue.
多棒呀 姑娘
Well, that is wonderful, girl.
迈开腿
Get your steps in!
不可以 不接受
Not all right, not okay!
没有助教就不能处
We don't have no teachers' aides!
不用担心 谢弗先生
Don't worry, Mr. Schaefer.
是 教职工们已经罢工两天了
Yes, the faculty has been on strike for two days
但学校还开着呢
but the school is still open.
我很高兴的告诉大家
And Im happy to report we've got
每个班级都有代班老师
substitutes for every class.
不是 我是说的代班
No, Isaid"substjtutes. "
我为什么要说我们有妓女啊
Why would I say we had prostitutes?
没有助教就不能处
PROTESTERS: We don't have no teacher's aiidesl
她是打电话呢吗
Is she on the phone?
嘿 嘿 吼 吼
Hey, heyl Ho, ho!
我们才不管你打着电话呢
We donft care youlre on the phonel
嘿 嘿 吼 吼
Hey, heyl Ho, hol
我们才不管你打着电话呢
We dorjt care you're on the phonel
欢迎来到街区 欢迎来到邻里
♪ Welcome to the block welcome to the neighborhood ♪
欢迎来跟我们做邻居
♪ Welcome to the hood.
戴夫
Um, Dave?
戴夫 戴夫
Dave. David.
怎么
Yeah?
我跟你解释下吹叶机的科学原理哈
Let me explain the science of the Ieaf blower to you.
你应该是把草坪上的叶子吹掉
You're supposed to blow the Ieaves off your lawn,
而不是吹的满草坪都是
not back all over your lawn.
是 我是吹走了
Yeah, well, I already did that.
还整整齐齐地堆成堆了
But then they were all in a neat pile,
然后我就回屋里去了 而珍玛
and I was gonna have to go back inside and Gemma
现在并不让人愉悦
is not a pleasure right now.
我让她冷静一下 她却跟我说
And when I told her to calm down, she told me to...
该死
Damn.
珍玛说那话了
Gemma said that?
是啊 很过分
Yeah. It's bad.
我从没见过她气性这么大 一般来说 她生气的时候
I've never seen her this upset. Usually, when she's mad,
蒂娜会帮她消气 可现在
Tina helps her through it, but now
她生气的原因就是蒂娜
Tina is the reason she's mad.
是 是 蒂娜也在生珍玛气呢
Yeah, yeah, Tina is upset with Gemma, too.
你知道珍玛为庆祝我们周年纪念日
You know that five- piece china set
送我们的那套五件套瓷器吧
that Gemma got us for our anniversary?
现在不是三件套了吗
Is it now a three- piece china set?
或者是75件套瓷器 权看你怎么解读了
Or a 75- piece china set, depending on how you look at it.
戴夫 算不知道
Oh, Dave. I don't know
戴夫 真不知道
你干嘛还费事用那个吹叶机你
why you're bothering with that Ieaf blower.
你媳妇一天天的可能吹了
Your wife blows hot air all clay long.
蒂娜 蒂娜 别这样
Tina, Tina, come on.
嘿 戴夫 你能
Hey Dave, can you Oh.
我进去了
I'm going back inside.
别别别
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
我进屋
I'm going back inside.
I'm going. back inside
行啊 那我留外面 你进去
Fine, I'll stay and you go inside.
等等等等 珍玛 轮不着你来告诉我要干什么
Oh, wait, wait, wait, Gemma, you don't tell me what to do.
行呀 那就待外面呗 背后捅刀子的
Well, then fine, stay out here, backstabber.
-好吧 你知道吗 珍玛  -怎么  -你可以亲我
Okay, you know what, Gemma? You can kiss my What?
下地狱吧
Rot in hell!
还有你妈
And your mama! Oh!
戴夫 这可不是吹个叶子就能解决的事了
Dave, this is way bigger than leaves.
我们可能得重新规划下
We might have to relandscape out here.
也许建个泳池
Maybe put in a pool.
不要
Nope.
你干嘛呢
What are you doing?
扔几本书
Just getting rid of some books, man.
这些都让我想起了珍妮尔
These all remind me of Janelle.
别这样 大哥
Oh, come on, big bro.
我知道分手很难受
I know breakups are hard.
但真的够了
But enough already.
你把所有船长脆脆麦片都扔了
You threw out all the Cap'n Crunch.
她喜欢船长脆脆麦片
She loved Cap'n Crunch.
我还喜欢船长脆脆麦片呢
I love Cap'n Crunch.
所以我才买船长脆脆麦片的
That's why I bought the Cap'n Crunch.
听着 兄弟 我不理解
Look, man, I- I don't get it.
当初你俩在一起的时候 你看起来不像是要认真处
When you two were together, you didn't seem that serious.
现在她走了 你就变成没了她就活不了了
Now that she's gone, you can't live without her.
真爱就是这样的 马蒂
That's how true love works, Marty.
所以怎么着 你要把这些书都扔了呗
So, what, you're just gonna throw all these books away?
不是 我要把它们放到戴夫的小图书馆里
No, man, I'm gonna put em in Dave's little library.
真的吗 放那本
Really? The
《取悦黑人女性的秘密》进去
Secrets to Pleasing a Black Woman?
也许这本就不用了
Maybe not this one.
好吧
Okay.
好
-我天 又来了  -怎么啦
Oh, my God, okay, here we go. What?
我猜猜啊 马蒂 你喉咙痒
Let me guess, Marty you got a tickle in your throat,
就上网找医生 现在你觉得自己得了坏血病
you went on WebMD and now you think you have scurvy.
不是 我通过吃三个橘子排除了是坏血症
No. I eliminated scurvy by eating three oranges.
所以很明显这病要严重的多
So, clearly, this is something much worse.
马蒂 我给你买了锌片来
Marty, I brought you some zinc.
不行 退后 退后
Oh, no, stay back. Stay back!
我的N95口罩呢
Where are my N- 95 masks?
马尔科姆
Malcolm!
我猜猜
Oh, let me guess- -
口罩让你想起了珍妮尔
they reminded you of Janelle.
她喜欢戴粉色哒
She liked to wear the pink ones.
感冒而已 马蒂
It's just a cold, Marty.
这又不是《权力的游戏》你也没得灰鳞病
This isn't Game of Thrones. You don't have greyscale.
我们不会把你跟其他石人一起流放到
We're not gonna exile you to the ruins of Valyria
瓦雷利亚的废墟的
with the other stone men.
你啥都不知道 琼恩·雪诺
You know nothin", Jon Snow.
你最好习惯这事 考特尼
Oh, you better get used to this, Courtney.
马蒂很不擅长应对生病
Marty is very bad at being sick.
他九岁那年 要切扁桃体
You know, when he was nine, he had his tonsils out
他竟然写了份遗嘱
and he wrote a will.
他留给你什么了
What did he leave you?
什么都没留 他把一切都
Nothing. He left everything
留给美国扁桃体协会了
to the American Tonsil Society.
面那个协会并不存在
Which does not exist.
就该成立个
It should.
你最好振作起来
Well, you'd better rally.
明天我们还得去上婴儿安全课呢
We have our baby safety class tomorrow.
不不不 我去不了
Oh, no, no, no, I- I can't do that.
我都病成这样了 连自己脑袋都抬不起来
As sick as I am, I can barely lift up my own head.
更别提一个橡胶婴儿了
Let alone a rubber baby.
还有
Plus,
让所有那些胚胎暴露在我的瘟疫之下
it'd be irresponsible, exposing all those fetuses
是不负责任的行为
to my pestilence.
那课是爸爸妈妈们都要去的
It's for mothers and fathers.
我不想就跟孩子没爹一样
I don t want to go there looking like my baby
-自己过去  -马尔科姆可以去呀
doesn't have a father. Malcolm can go.
你又不知道我会不会有事
You don't know what Malcolm can do.
你有安排吗
Do you have plans?
你知道我没有的
You know I don't.
好 那么明天 你就是娃他爹
Okay, so, tomorrow, you the daddy.
嘿 蒂娜 我刚跟戴夫谈过
Hey, Tina, I was just talking to Dave
叛徒
Trajtor
戴夫来找我谈的
Well, Dave was talking to me.
就是 一堆废话
You know, Yap, yap, yap, yap.
但后来我听他说
But then I heard him say
珍玛意识到自己错了
that Gemma realizes that she was wrong.
蒂娜·巴特勒真的有说她错了
So, Tina Butler actually said she was wrong?
我自己也不敢信
I couldn't believe it myself.
但卡尔文就是这么跟我说的
But that's what Calvin told me.
那她为什么不亲自来跟我说
So, why didn't she tell me herself?
她害怕你听到后的反应
She was afraid of how you would react.
怎么 被人告知我是对的
What, to being told Im right?
是 她意识到你是对的
Yes, she realizes you were right.
她想一起吃顿晚饭 把问题解决掉
She wants to get together for dinner to work things out.
好吧 我觉得让她有机会道歉
Okay. Well, I guess the right thing to do
是正确的做法
would be to Iet her apologize
我倒是可以听她道歉啦
Well, I guess I could listen to her apology.
太好了 这样吧
Great. You know what,
咱可以在咱家吃晚饭把这事办了
we'll do it here over dinner.
好
Okay.
但我不做饭哈
But Im not cooking.
当然不是你做了
Of course not.
这么说蒂娜会做饭喽
So, Tina's cooking?
她坚持
She insisted.
好吧 挺好
Okay, good.
我是生她气但我不气她做的小排骨
I'm mad at her, but Im not mad at her short ribs.
是
Yeah.
好
AlI right.
开吃吧
Here we go.
-走起  -这是泰式炒面
Jump in. This is pad thai.
总比小排骨强吧 你不觉得吗
Better thah short ribs, don't you think?
不觉得
No.
你侮辱完食物之后
Well, when you're done insulting the food,
也许有话想跟我说
maybe there's something you want to say to me?
我想先等你说
I want to accept something
然后我再接受
after you say something to me.
这算哪门子道歉
What kind of apology is this?
我为什么要道歉
Why would I have an apology?
这个趋势很好
DAVE: Well, this is healthy.
大家提“道歉”这个词的概率很高
The word "apology" is being·thrown around a lot.
珍玛
TINA: Gemma?
除非给我们配助教 罢工是不会结束的
This strike is not going to end until we have teachers'aides.
可你在一直无视这个问题
But you keep ignoring the issue.
我并没有无视
I am not ignoring it.
就是 有时候就是要做出很艰难的决定
It's just, sometimes tough decisions have to be made.
卡尔文 你听这像话吗
Calvin, do you hear this craziness?
不像话
CALVIN: Crazy.
是
Yes.
但是 说句公道话
But, in all fairness,
负责预算的人做决定挺难的
it is tough when you're in charge of the budget.
我在熔丝盒一直都要处理这样的问题
I have to deal with that all the time at the Fusebox.
好的 那么在熔丝盒
Okay, okay. So, at the Fusebox
你有让你们软件工程师
do you make your software engineers
负责烘焙义卖吗
run the bake sale?
其实
CALVIN: Well, actually,
-并不像是  -是这样
it's not like th...DAVE: Well, you know, uh,
蒂娜提的一些观点确实挺合理的
Tina does make some reasonable points.
什么
What? !
我只是想说啊
DAVE: I'm just saying,
你雇员工是来做一件事
you hire an employee to do a job,
而不是样样都做
not every job
没错
Exactly.
我不该午休时间
I should not be coaching kickball
教踢球
during my lunch break.
我高跟鞋一直陷进人造草皮
I mean, my high heels keep punching through the Astroturf.
我理解 但是
CALVIN: I get that, but
有时候 当你处于领导层
sometimes, when you're in management,
就不得不要求你的团队为了
you have to ask your team to go the extra mile
公司利益多做些事
for the good of the business.
谢谢 加尔文
Thank you, Calvin.
但所有组织里
But any organization's
最宝贵的资源都是已经在战壕里的人
most valuable resource is the people in the trenches.
靠 戴夫 来击个掌
Damn it, Davel Give me some.
好吧
Okay
戴夫 这件事的重点是
Dave, the whole point of this
你应该同意我观点
was that you were to agree with me.
错 我们是同意我们同意的观点
No, we just agreed to agree.
我从没同意过跟你意见一致
I never agreed to agree with you.
真不敢相信你站蒂娜那边
I can't believe your're on Tina's side.
那是因为戴夫有同情心
That's because Dave has empathy for people.
他不会像你和卡尔文一样
He doesn't work them till their fingers bleed
榨干大家的工作价值
like you and Calvin.
-好吧  -听我说 好了
Okay. CALVIN: Uh, listen, okay, all right.
珍玛和我理解身为管理层
Uh, Gemma and I just understand what it is
应该是什么样子 好吗
to be management, all right?
你们必须要着眼大局
You just have to look at the bigger picture.
正是 卡尔文和我
Exactly. Calvin and I
是那种顾全大局的人
are big- picture people:
听见没 戴夫
You hear this, Dave?
看来咱们格局都小了呗
I guess we're just little- ass picture people.
我没这时间跟你们掰扯
I ain't got no time for thisl
你知道吗
You know what?
我也没这时间
I ain't got no time for this, either.
永远团结
Solidarity forever.
卡尔文 看来我也该走了
Well, Calvin, I guess I better go too
不用 别 珍玛 留下
No, no, no, Gemma, stay.
好吧 某些人不理解商业运作
AlI right? It's not our fault that some people
不是我们的错 好吗
don't understand business, all right?
我们配得上这份烤肉 来 给 吃吧
We deserve this satay. Here, here, come on.
就是 还得多加花生酱
Yes. With extra peanut sauce.
没错 酱汁加起来
That's right, sauce me up.
-好  -卡尔文 你最好
Yep. TINA: Calvin, you better
马上滚到我房间
sauce your ass in this rooml
-你还是打包带走吧 快走  -好
You might want to take that to go. Get on out of here. Yeah.
天
Oh, God.
戴夫 你这是干嘛
Dave, what are you doing?
给你唱小夜曲 因为你生我气了
Serenading you, because you're mad at me.
这样没用的
It's not working.
你话是这么说
Well, so you say,
可你永远无法抗拒我的“噢酷嘞嘞”
but you can never resist my"ooh- koo- lay- lay. "
跟其他人一样说“尤克里里”
Say "ukulele" like everyone else.
人家在“虾威夷“可不是这么说的
That's not how they say it in"Ooh- vah- ee. "
我只是希望你能理解
I just wish you could understand
我现在有多大压力
how much stress I'm under right now.
快点妈 我不想上学迟到
Come on, Mom, I don't want to be late for school.
我的新科学老师可赞了
Uh, my new science teacher is awesome.
很好呀
That's great
看到没 格罗弗喜欢代班老师
See? Grover loves the substitutes.
跟你那个小同志蒂娜讲 想怎么罢工随她
Tell your little comrade Tina to strike all she wants.
我的学校课照上
We're still learning at my school.
特别酷 我学到了很多占星术的知识
It is so cool. I've learned so much about astrology.
-你是说天文学  -什
You mean astronomy. Wh
不可能 天文学是伪科学
No way. Astronomy is pseudoscience.
它完全无视了行星的排列
It completely ignores how the alignment of planets
是如何预测我们未来的爱情生活的
predicts our future love lives.
-你还希望我去跟蒂娜讲吗  -说个试试
You still want me to talk to Tina? - Don't you dare.
妈咪 鸡汤什么病都治不了
Mommy, chicken soup is not a cure for anything.
不过就是盐 脂肪还有一点胡萝卜
It's just salt and fat and little bits of carrots.
还有爱
And love.
好吧 行 还有爱 但是
Okay, fine, it- it's got love in it, too, but still,
我还是要遵循科学的
I'm following the science.
我买了个蒸汽机 一个雾化器 一个喷雾器
I got a vaporizer, an atomizer, a nebulizer.
你想用科学方式 只要在脚上涂点维克斯伤风膏就行
You want science, just put some Vicks VapoRub on your feet.
这怎么就是科学方式了
How is that science?
你往脚上涂完维克斯伤风膏
You put the Vicks on your feet,
穿上袜子
you put on some socks,
伤风膏会经过你的脚
the Vicks sucks all the cold
把你身体里所有寒气都吸出来
out of your body, through your feet,
释放到袜子里
and into the socks.
但是妈咪
But, Mommy
马蒂 拜托 别再浪费我时间了
Marty, please, stop wasting my time.
我已经在跟我最好的朋友吵架了
I've already been fighting my best frjend.
我不会跟你吵架的
I am not about to fight you.
我只是不想把病传染给我孩子
I just don't want to get my baby sick.
孩子会让你生病的
The baby is gonna make you sick.
什么
What?
好吧 马蒂
Oh, okay, Marty.
孩子会把世界上所有的
The baby's gonna bring every germ
细菌都带进你家
in the world into your house.
等孩子从托儿所回来 咳嗽的时候
When the baby comes home from day care, coughing,
会把鼻涕糊的
it's gonna have snot caked all over
整张小脸蛋都是 然后
its little face, and then Oh!
直接冲着你嘴里打喷嚏
sneeze right into your mouth.
不
No.
会的
Yes.
而你还得照顾小孩
And you're gonna have to take care of the kid.
所以你最好习惯会一直生病
So you better get used to being sick all the damn time.
把你大人裤子穿上 把伤风膏袜子套上
So. Put your big boy pants on, put your Vapo- socks on
准备好扛过这场病吧 孩儿他爹
and get ready to power through it, dacdy.
好吧好吧 我可以的
Okay. Okay, all right, I can do this.
你可以 你当然可以了
Yes, you can. You sure can.
但你知道吗 但我听说
But you know what, when I heard
我家小宝贝生病了的时候
my little baby boy was sick,
就放下一切 冲回家开始做饭
I dropped everything, ran home and started cooking.
现在张开嘴
Now open your mouth
喝点汤进去
and put some soup in it
康纳 格雷森 很高兴你们能来 欢迎
Connor, Graycen, nice to have you, welcome.
下一位
Next.
我叫乔丹 这是我丈夫杰
I'm Jordan. This is my husband Jay
我们现在怀孕32周了
And we're at, oh, my God, 32 weeks.
妤的 快卸货了哈 下一位
Well, okay, you're getting close. Next.
-你好 我是考特尼  -我是马尔科姆
Hi, I'm Courtney. I'm Malcolm.
您二位怀了多久啦
And how far along are you two?
不是 我俩不是两囗子
Oh, no, we are not a two.
行吧 就是说您二位没结婚
Okay, so you're not married,
但你想参与到这个孩子的生产当中来
but you're gonna be an involved dad?
不是 我什么都没参与
Oh, no, I am not involved at all.
实际上 我跟任何人 都没啥关系
In fact, I'm not involved with, uh, with anyone.
他是我宝宝的爸爸的哥哥
He's my baby's father's brother.
相同的DNA 没掺杂到一起去
Same DNA, no smashing.
我之前确实跟 某人有点关系
You know, I was involved, uh, with someone,
最近才没有的
until very, very recently,
但我 是我把一切都扔掉的
but, uh, yeah, II threw that all away.
跟个傻瓜似的
Like a fool.
不必自责
Aw, donjt beat yourself up.
是 都是我的错
Yeah, it was all my fault.
但是我在努力
But- but I'm trying, you know.
努力让自己成为一个更好的人
I'm trying to make myself a, uh, a better man.
而我在努力让我孩子活下来
And I'm trying to keep my baby alive.
我们能回到正题了吗
So, can we get back to that part?
好的 是 好 各位
Yes. Right. Okay, uh, everybody,
抱起你们的宝宝 我们练习下怎么抱他们
pick up your babies and let's practice cradling them.
好 我们
Yeah. Let's
马尔科姆叔叔
Uncle Malcolm,
不要拎腿
you don't pick them up by the leg.
能再给我们个宝宝吗
Can we get another baby?
或者来卷胶带
Or some duct tape?
嘿 卡尔文 看来蒂娜还在生我气呢
Hey, Calvin. Tina's still mad, I see.
你怎么知道的
Eh. How'd you know?
她一生气你就会来鼓捣你的车
You always work on your truck when she's mad.
你给她买了职业橄榄球联盟周日赛事套票那次
Like on her birthday, when you got her NFL Sunday Ticket.
是 那次之后 我跟这车身上鼓捣了一个月
Yeah, I worked on this truck for a month after that one.
不过我挺喜欢修车的
You know, I like being back under the hood, though.
这是让我开心的地方
It's my happy place.
不是吧 你个该死的电线
Aah! Come on, you stupid cord.
我知道你的感受
Yeah, I know how you feel.
我今天上了六节课
I had to teach six classes today.
自打我们搬来这里我就没教过课
I haven't taught a class since we moved here.
那帮孩子吵吵闹闹的 还顶嘴
The kids were screaming and talking back
毫无注意力可言
and they have no attention span at all.
我都有点忘了教书有多难了
Kind of forgot how hard teaching is.
是啊 蒂娜就这么说的
Yeah, that's what Tina says.
但我也忘了我有多爱教书
But I also forgot how much I love it.
她也这么说的
She says that, too.
她有说吗
She does?
是啊
Yeah.
她当然会这么说了
Of course she does.
我怎么就让事情发展到这步了呢
How did I let it get this far?
我不知道 你们这份工作压力很大
I don't know. You guys have a very stressful job.
因为就我个人而言
Cause, personally,
我是不喜欢别人家小孩的
I don't like other people's kids.
格罗弗呢
What about Grover?
我是说不住在这个街区的别人家小孩
I'm talking about other people that's not on this block.
我现在看明白了
Now it's so clear to me.
我之前就是坠入爱河了
I was falling in love.
但那把我吓坏了
But that scared me so badly
于是就把她推开了
that I pushed her away.
现在 不管我去到哪儿
And now, everywhere I go,
不管做什么 都会萦绕在心头
everything I do- - it haunts me.
会去想可能会发生什么
The thought of what could have been.
大兄弟
Oh, brother.
你一定要原谅自己
You have to forgive yourself.
我尽力了 洛林
You know, I'm trying, Lorraine.
但我还有很长的路要走
But I got a long way to go.
你会成功的
You'll get there.
我知道你会的
I know you will.
谢谢
Thank you.
教学大纲上说我们
The syllabus said we would
现在要学做心肺复苏了 所以
get to CPR by now, so...
你是个好人 马尔科姆
You're a good guy, Malcolm.
相信我 总有一天
And, trust me, someday,
一个优秀的女人会看到这一切的
a great woman is going to see all of that.
谁知道呢 也许
I mean, who knows, maybe
她了解关于宝宝们的一切
she knows everything about babies
可自己却没有孩子
but doesn't have any herself.
目前还没有
Yet
我希望有这么个人
I hope she's out there.
她比你想象的还要近在眼前
She's closer than you can imagine
我只想说 鉴于
I'm just saying, because
我们只剩20分钟了
we only have 20 minutes left
我觉得你跳过了很多内容
and I think you skipped over a lot of stuff.
现在不是在聊你
This isn't about you.
嗨 蒂娜
Hi, Tina.
珍玛
Gemma.
有几句话我想对你说
I have something I need to say to you.
我对罢工这事并不满意 但信我
I'm not happy about the strike, but believe me,
我理解教书很难
I understand that teaching is hard
我不喜欢自己竟然成了个
and I hate that I somehow became
书呆子官僚主义者
a pencil- necked bureaucrat.
-你刚说你理解  -是
Did you say you understand? - Yes.
我觉得我只是忘了什么才是最重
I guess Ijust lost sight of what's really imp...
我也爱你
I love you, too.
-这也太蠢了  -你是我最好的朋友  -这太扯了 对不起
This is so dumbl You're my best friendl This is crazy! I'm sorryl
-我爱你  -我好想你呀
- I love you! I missed you so much!
我会纠正的
I'm gonna make this right.
我会让老师们得到他们应有的支持
I am gonna get the teachers the support they deserve.
这意味着要跟董事会表明立场
A- And that means taking a stand with the board of trustees.
我可能会被解雇
And I may get fired
什么
Uh, what?
我倒希望他们炒你呢 让他们炒个试试
I wish they would. Let them try to fire you.
你以为罢工就够受的了哈
You thought that strike was bad?
我们会把那里夷为平地的
We'll burn that place to the ground.
行吧 淡定
Okay. Okay, easy now.
那次罢工是真把你勾起来了
That strike has really got you worked up.
但我很开心有你支持
But I'm glad to know you have my back.
我一直都会支持你的
Always.
现在
Now.
-你想一醉方休吗  -想
You want to get drunk? Yes, please.
瞧瞧你 生龙活虎的
Look at you up and around.
是 我重生了
Yup. I'm a new man.
我闻到伤风膏的味了
I smell Vicks
妈妈给你脚上涂了
Did Mama do yourfeet?
是
Yeah.
也涂胸口了
My chest, too.
但她也给了我些严厉的爱
But she also gave me some tough love,
就比如为人父母就是份24小肘不间断的工作
Iike being a parent is a 24 hour a day job.
如果我自己都长不大 就没办法做好这份工
I- Iwon't be able to handle it if I act like a baby,
所以这可能是最后一次让妈妈涂胸了
so that might be my last chest rub.
不行 是时候了
No it's time.
20年前就该这样了
It's been time for 20 years.
几位 卡尔文在套圈摊子上大杀四方
You guys, Calvin killed it at the ring toss booth.
都跟你说了 这得看腕劲
I told you, it's all in the wrist.
现在我要带只金鱼回家啦
And now I'm bringing home the gold.
爸 那条金鱼你打算怎么处理
Dad, what are you gonna do with that goldfish?
没想好
I don't know.
就是觉得扔垃圾桶里不大合适
Just don't feel right throwing it in the trash.
抱歉 兄弟
Sorry, buddy,
-你跟那东西绑定了  -是啊
you are stuck with that thing. Yeah.
给你 格罗弗
Oh, here you go, Grover. Oh.
谢谢 卡尔文先生 爸 我们得买个鱼缸
Thanks, Mr. Calvin. Uh, Dad, we need a fish tank.
-是 买  -好
Yeah, we do. Yup
教职工罢工这事怎么解决的
Oh, so how'd the teacher strike get settled?
珍玛跟老师们一统一战线
Oh, well, once Gemma and the teachers were on the same side,
董事会就没机会了
board didn't stamd a chance.
是呢 我闺蜜珍玛给我们争取到了我们想要的一切
Yeah, my girl Gemma gave us everything we wanted.
我很开心所有老师
Hell, I'm just glad all of the teachers
跟珍玛冰释前嫌
are cool with Gemma again.
我好怕怕呀
Ooh, I'm scared.
你就这点本事呀 瑞恩
Is that all you got, Ryan?
来呀 打领结的人是不可能把我打倒的
Come on, nobody in a bow tie can take me down.
你好刻薄啊
You're mean.
就是这架势
CALVIN; That's what I'm talking about.
希望你会游泳 金发妞
Hope you can swjm, blondie.
不是吧 这里就没人能打倒校长吗
Come on. Is there nobody here who can take down the principal?
-好 来  -蒂娜
5 AlI right, come on. GEMMA: Oh, Tina?
就你那小劲儿就别扔了吧
Please. Don't bring that weak sauce to my tank.
行呀
Okay.
不要啊
Oh, no.
拜啦 邻居
Bye, neighbor.